https://www.epwealth.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

Why EP?
800.272.2328
Why EP?
EP Wealth Advisors, LLC Customer Information Privacy Policy
Like most industries today, the financial services industry is rapidly being shaped by technology, which is changing the way we dobusiness. To be successful in this environment, we must continue to ensure that we will manage our customer’s financial affairspragmatically and confidentially. At EP Wealth Advisors, LLC our customers have access to a broad range of investments and services.To deliver these products and services as effectively and conveniently as possible, it is essential that we use current technology tomanage and maintain certain customer information. We want to assure all our customers that whenever information is used, it is donewith discretion, integrity, and conforming to high security standards. The safeguarding of customer information is an issue we takeseriously at EP Wealth Advisors, LLC. To affirm our continuing commitment to the proper use of customer information, we have set forththe following Privacy Policy. It is this Privacy Policy that guides us in serving the privacy needs of our customers.
1. California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”): The CCPA is a piece of legislation that provides California residents rightsover the information collected and retained by business like ours. At EP Wealth Advisors, LLC we believe the standards established bythe CCPA should apply to all our customers, irrespective of where they reside. As outlined below, our clients have the right to know: thetype information we collect, right to delete the information we collect – subject to an exception, and right to opt out of Sale of thatinformation.
2. Recognition of a Customer’s Expectation of Privacy: At EP Wealth Advisors, LLC we believe the confidentiality and protection ofcustomer information is a fundamental responsibility. While information is critical to providing quality service, we recognize that one ofour most important assets is customer trust and confidence. Thus, the safekeeping of customer information is a priority.
3. Collection and Retention of Customer Information: EP Wealth Advisors, LLC limits the use, collection, and retention of customerinformation which is necessary or useful to effectively conduct business and provide quality service to our clients. Information collectedmay include but is not limited to: a client(s) name, address, telephone number, tax identification number or social security number, date ofbirth, employment status, annual income, net worth, financial statements and previous tax filings, estate documents, insuranceinformation, and more.
4. Maintenance of Accurate Information: EP Wealth Advisors, LLC recognizes that it must maintain accurate customer records.Therefore, EP Wealth Advisors has established procedures to maintain the accuracy of customer information and to keep suchinformation current and complete. These procedures include responding to requests to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner.
5. Limiting Employee Access to Information: At EP Wealth Advisors, LLC employee access to personally identifiable customerinformation is limited to those with a business reason to know such information. Employees are educated on the importance ofmaintaining the confidentiality of customer information and on the Privacy Policy. Because of the importance of these issues, all EPWealth Advisors employees are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of customer information and employees who violate thePrivacy Policy will be subject to disciplinary measures.
6. Protection of Information via Established Security Procedures: EP Wealth Advisors, LLC recognizes that a fundamental elementof maintaining effective customer privacy procedures is to provide reasonable protection against the unauthorized access to customerinformation. Therefore, EP Wealth Advisors, Inc. has established appropriate security standards and procedures to guard against anyunauthorized access to customer information.
7. Restrictions on the Disclosure or Sell of Customer Information: When it comes to sharing or selling customer information withunaffiliated companies, EP Wealth Advisors places strict limits on who receives specific information about customer accounts and otherpersonally identifiable data. EP Wealth Advisors may share information with unaffiliated companies that in the normal course of ourbusiness assist in providing investments and critical services to our customers only. Additionally, only in situations when legally requiredor permitted in connection with fraud investigations or litigation; in connection with acquisitions and sales; and at the request or with thepermission of a customer only.
8. Maintaining Customer Privacy in Business Relationships with Third Parties: If we provide personally identifiable customerinformation to a third party with which we have a business relationship, we will insist that the third party keep such information confidential,consistent with the conduct of our business relationship and subject to a Non-Disclosure Agreement and/or Confidentiality Clauses.
9. Provision of Opt Out: EP Wealth Advisors currently operates under a “do not share” and “do not sell” policy. Therefore, given ourstrict policy, we do not need to provide the right for its clients to opt out of sharing or selling with nonaffiliated third parties.
10. Disclosure of Privacy Policy to Customers: EP Wealth Advisors, LLC recognizes and respects the privacy expectations of ourcustomers. We want our customers to understand our commitment to privacy in our use of customer information. As a result of ourcommitment, we have developed this Privacy Policy which we made readily available to our customers. Customers who have questionsabout the Privacy Policy, want to request a detailing of the information we maintain on their behalf or have a question about the privacyof their customer information should call us at (310) 543-4559 or e-mail us at info@epwealth.com.
The Privacy Policy applies to individuals, and we reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy and any of the policies or procedures described above, at any timewithout prior notice. The Privacy Policy is intended for general guidance and does not constitute a contract or create legal rights and does not modify or amend any agreements we have with our customers.
© 2020 EP Wealth Advisors
Privacy Policy
Careers
Disclosures
Form CRS
Form ADV Part 2A
